Yakkan title
Now, the second element that makes an idol star like that is dance.
Dance.
But you have an image of that, don't you?
Really?
I really love dancing. I love to dance and I love to watch,
I didn't really like dancing when I was a member of 3BJr.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I wasn't good at it, and I didn't want to dance in front of everyone,
But then I got to be a back-up dancer for Arline's solo concert,
I started to spend more time with dance. And there, I realized that dancing is fun.
That's when I started to think that dancing is fun,
Now I love dancing the most.
There were some specific things that I had to do in terms of time,
Was there something about the way you presented yourself?
Was there a turning point for you?
Yes, it was. The more you practice, the better you get.
That's what free videotapes are for. The manager would take videos of my lessons.
When I watched them, I saw that the way I danced was changing more and more,
I really enjoyed those changes,
I started to study in front of the mirror, thinking about how I wanted to show it better,
I started to study in front of the mirror, thinking about what I wanted to show more like, and I started getting compliments on it,
I started getting compliments on it, and I realized that dancing is so much fun.
I see.
It was fun to practice.
It is true that your expression has changed since then.
Really?
And then people outside the company saw it at Stamp Fest and other events,
I knew it was true because of what you said.
So you do it at home.
I don't have a big mirror, so I turn off the TV and reflect myself.
Isn't that right?
Is that how you use the F-show TV?
Yes, it is.
It gets dark at night, so the windows also become mirrors.
It might be a common practice for dancers,
Can you do F-show TV at home?
Yes, I do.
Yes, because I'm being filmed.
My face will be a little cut off because of the reflection, but if I stand up, I'll be able to see it.
I don't get involved, but it would be nice to see.
If there was a bigger mirror,
If I had a bigger mirror, I would add more facial expressions.
Lately, I've been paying a lot of attention to expression management.
Expression management.
I've been trying to make funny faces.
I try to make funny faces.
I also try to make funny faces,
I also use a nighttime body, but it shows various images, so it is already a phase.
I'm not good at it at home, but I'm doing it.
I'm not very good at it, but I'm doing it at home.
This video was provided by Mr. Toy.
Thank you very much.